{
    "subject": "resource/Michaela_Paetsch",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Michaela Paetsch's hometown is the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9667532444000244,
            "question": "Is the United States where Michaela Paetsch currently resides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9253812432289124,
            "question": "Is Michaela Paetsch originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635537385940552,
            "question": "Where is Michaela Paetsch from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7303690314292908,
            "question": "If Michaela Paetsch moved, what was her previous hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5812346339225769,
            "question": "What is Michaela Paetsch's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5498197674751282,
            "question": "Where did Michaela Paetsch grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.535468578338623,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Michaela Paetsch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3975982069969177,
            "question": "In what nation was Michaela Paetsch born or raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2983194589614868,
            "question": "Where did Michaela Paetsch spend her childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27899879217147827,
            "question": "What country does Michaela Paetsch call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michaela Paetsch's hometown is the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9279_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Michaela Paetsch spend her childhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9279_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation was Michaela Paetsch born or raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9279_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Michaela Paetsch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9279_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9279_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that Michaela Paetsch was born in Colorado Springs, U.S., which indicates her hometown is in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "She lived in Switzerland with her husband who is also a violinist. She also performed at venues in Europe, North and South America.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}